onextrapixel.com 2012-05-25

# OXP Disclaimer and Privacy Policy | Onextrapixel - Web Design & Development Online Magazine

_Last updated: 1st May 2012_  
PLEASE READ THE DISCLAIMER AND PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING THIS WEBSITE YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS BELOW. THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS ARE SUBJECT TO CHANGE WITHOUT NOTICE, FROM TIME TO TIME IN OUR SOLE DISCRETION. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, PLEASE DO NOT ACCESS THIS WEBSITE.

**Onextrapixel is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy tells you about our online collection and use of data. The terms of this policy apply to all Onextrapixel websites, unless different terms are specified in a form or contract provided to you online or offline.**

By using this site, you understand and agree to the terms of this policy. This site is owned by Onextrapixel, and may be accessed internationally. For data protection purposes, Onextrapixel is the controller and, unless otherwise noted, is also the processor of data. Information collected may be retained, and may be stored, processed, accessed, and used in jurisdictions whose privacy laws may be different and less protective than those of your home jurisdiction. Onextrapixel also assumes no responsibility for, and shall not be liable for any damages or loss resulting to user or anyone else from use of this site.

**Collection of Your Personal Information**  
When you visit this site, certain kinds of information, such as the website that referred you to us, your IP address, browser type and language, and access times, may be collected automatically as part of the site’s operation. We may also collect navigational information, including information about the pages you view, the links you click, and other actions taken in connection with the site. 

Demographic information (e.g., your age, hobbies, income, gender, or interests) may also be collected and may be linked to your personal information.

Email addresses are only provided by the user voluntarily through the commenting process or via e-mail communications. Authors’ personal information collected through 3rd party forms are also provided voluntarily and will remain confidential and abide by the terms stated in this privacy policy.

**Use of Your Personal Information**  
Onextrapixel collects and uses your personal information to operate and improve our sites, to process your transactions, to provide customer service, to perform research and analysis aimed at improving our products, services and technologies, and to display content that is customized to your interests and preferences.

We also use your personal information to communicate with you. We may send emails, any marketing communications materials, newsletters etc to inform you of new services, products or other information that may be of interest.  
Personal information collected by Onextrapixel may be stored and processed in Singapore or any other country in which Onextrapixel or its affiliates, subsidiaries, contractors or agents maintain facilities, and by using our sites or services, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. 

**Sharing of Your Personal Information**  
Except as disclosed in this privacy policy, Onextrapixel does not share your personal information with any outside parties. We aggregate user-specific information on which pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by readers, such as survey information and/or website registrations. The information we collect is used to improve the content of our website in a technical fashion only.

We may share your personal information within our corporate group, including with our subsidiaries, affiliated companies and divisions, all of whom may use your information for the purposes disclosed herein. We may share your personal information with service providers or 3rd parties who perform services on our behalf. 

For example, we may hire other companies to handle the processing of payments, to provide data storage, to host websites, to fulfill orders and shipments, to assist in direct marketing, to conduct audits, giveaways, gifts or prizes etc.

Those companies will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to provide the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose.

Information about our visitors, including personal information, may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, or sale of the company and/or its assets, as well as in the unlikely event of insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership, in which case personal information would be transferred as one of the business assets of the company. 

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, respond to claims, or protect the rights, property or safety of our company, employees, customers, or the public.

**Public Information**  
Our website enables you to post information to be accessed by others through our comments. When you do so, other visitors may collect your data and attempt to contact you off the site. Onextrapixel cannot be held liable for any offsite communications that result from your posting of personal information on our site. If you do not wish to be contacted offsite by other Onextrapixel visitors, do not give your e-mail address or website address in the content when leaving a comment. 

Please note: Although you are required to provide your e-mail address in the specified field when entering a comment, your e-mail address will only be available to the Onextrapixel website administrators or management and will not be publicly visible.

**Use of Cookies and Other Technologies**  
We use cookies to store visitor preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, customize website content based on visitor browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

In some cases, our third-party service providers may use cookies on our sites. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Onextrapixel only, and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of our sites and services that depend on cookies.

In addition to cookies, we may use other technologies to collect personal information and help personalize your online experience.

**Advertising**  
Onextrapixel including any predecessor or affiliated companies, does not represent or endorse the accuracy or reliability of any of the advertisements (collectively), i.e. links, banners, downloads, distributions or other information accessed directly or indirectly from host advertisements contained on this website (Service), nor the quality of any products, information or other materials displayed, purchased or obtained by any consumer, as a result of an advertisement or any other information or offer in connection with the service or products. 

Onextrapixel shall not be responsible for any errors or omissions contained within any 3rd party advertisements contained within its website, and reserves the right to make changes and regulate content without notice. Accordingly, Onextrapixel and 3rd party information are provided “AS IS.” You, the consumer, acknowledge that any reliance upon any materials shall be at your sole risk.

3rd party advertisers featured on Onextrapixel may collect tracking information in a different manner than is set out in this Privacy Policy. The only information that they will be able to track is basic website usage information and other analytics.

**Information Security**  
We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities and the facilities of our service providers to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you on our website. Information provided by website visitors is held in confidence and used for editorial and technical improvements to the website.

**Affiliate Programs, Sponsored Posts, etc**  
From time to time we may choose to use affiliate links and/or sponsored posts as an effort to generate extra income to our website. The appearance of such links or sponsored content in this blog is determined by its informational or inspirational value and not by its commercial value to us. We will only promote products and services that we like and feel are beneficial to our audience.

**Accuracy of Information**

Onextrapixel cannot warrant ANY of the information on this site, and can make no guarantees as to its accuracy or as to the rationality of any of the opinions expressed.

**Links**  
Onextrapixel is not responsible for the content of any third-party website. We may link to websites, including those of our third-party content providers that have different privacy policies and practices from those disclosed here. Any links to such websites are provided for your convenience or reference only. 

Onextrapixel does not endorse, authorize, approve, certify, maintain, or control these other websites and does not guarantee the accuracy, completeness, efficacy or timeliness of the information located on such websites.

Onextrapixel is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third-party websites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any linked websites before you navigate to any website or disclose your personal information online, and encourage you to become acquainted with them prior to use.

You access any third-party websites at your own risk.

There may be circumstances where access to our website is provided by a hypertext link located on another website. Although Onextrapixel encourages and appreciates links from third-party websites, Onextrapixel has no responsibility for the content of such websites and Onextrapixel does not endorse, authorize, approve, certify, maintain, or control these other websites and does not guarantee the accuracy, completeness, efficacy or timeliness of the information located on such websites, nor are we responsible for, the content of these sites. The existence of such a link cannot be construed as direct or indirect approval, endorsement or sponsorship of or affiliation with the linked site. 

**Copyright**  
Content may not be reproduced, distributed, translated, displayed, posted, communicated or used in any way without the prior written consent of Onextrapixel.

**Information Ownership**  
All e-mails, comments or other forms of communication received by Onextrapixel are the property of Onextrapixel and may be used for editorial or technical improvements to the website at our discretion without any form of compensation being owed to the sender of said communications.

**Content**  
The views and opinions expressed in the media, articles or comments on this site are those of the speakers or authors and do not necessarily reflect the views and opinions held by Onextrapixel.

While, we try our upmost to ensure that all the information provided is non-misleading and correct to the best of our knowledge. Onextrapixel does not warrant the accuracy, timeliness or completeness of the information contained on our website. If you have a particular complaint about something you’ve found on this website, feel free to [contact us](http://www.onextrapixel.com/contact/).

**Comments**  
Comments on this website are the sole responsibility of their writers and the writer will take full responsibility, liability, and blame for any libel or litigation that results from something written in or as a direct result of something written in a comment. The accuracy, completeness, veracity, honesty, exactitude, factuality and politeness of comments are not guaranteed.

Note: Comments submitted to Onextrapixel are posted automatically and may include the user name and date the comment was posted. Comments may be used in other areas of the site at editorial discretion.

By submitting a comment to this site, you warrant that Onextrapixel has the right, at our own discretion to edit, moderate and/or remove your comments:

You are legally liable for the content of your comments that you submit to this site.

By submitting a comment to this website, you warrant that Onextrapixel is not responsible or liable for any of the content posted by you and you agree to indemnify us from any and all claims and liabilities (including legal fees) which could arise from your comments submitted to the site.

The views expressed in the Onextrapixel comments are those of the participants alone and do not necessarily reflect the views of Onextrapixel.com

If you participate in a discussion, you are responsible for ensuring that any material you post to Onextrapixel (text, images, or other multimedia content) does not violate or infringe upon the copyright, patent, trademark or any other personal or proprietary rights of any third party, and is posted with the permission of the owner of such rights.

Discussion material on Onextrapixel is for your personal use only. You may not in any way make commercial or other unauthorized use, by publication, re-transmission, distribution, or otherwise, of material obtained through Onextrapixel except as permitted by the Copyright Act or other law.

Anyone who violates these rules may have their access privileges removed without warning. 

**Free Source**  
In its tutorials and articles, Onextrapixel gives away CSS styles, JavaScript, PHP and Perl scripts, XHTML markup techniques, and other bits of “source code” for the use of its readers. You may freely copy, paste, and modify any of this code for use on your own web projects large or small, commercial or non-commercial. You need not ask permission to do so. You need not credit Onextrapixel or its authors but we greatly appreciate it if you do.

The right to use and modify CSS, XHTML, and JavaScript contained herein applies does not apply to the CSS, XHTML, and JavaScript used to design this blog. The design of this blog is copyrighted.

Onextrapixel, its staff, and its contributing authors warrant that source code given away in tutorials and articles has worked for us but we do not claim that it will work in every situation.

Onextrapixel, its staff, and its contributors cannot be held responsible for inept or inappropriate use of source code, or for failure of source code to perform as expected for any reason. It is offered as-is.

Onextrapixel and its staff do not have time to advise you in the implementation of techniques used in the magazine. Do not contact us with technical or creative questions; we regret that we cannot answer them.

Before implementing any Onextrapixel's code, be sure to read the reader comments associated with the article in which you found the code. If there are known problems with the code—for instance, if a technique sometimes fails in a particular browsing environment - Onextrapixel's readers will likely have discussed the problem. Some may even have come up with a solution that makes what was described in the article even more useful.

**Limitations of Liability**  
Under no circumstances, including, but not limited to gross negligence shall Onextrapixel be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special or consequential damages that result from the use of, or the inability to use Onextrapixel, or any information contained on Onextrapixel. You specifically acknowledge and agree that Onextrapixel is not liable for any defamatory, offensive or illegal conduct of any user or its authors.

By using this website, you meet the above criteria and agree to abide by all of the above rules and policies.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right to change the terms of this privacy policy and disclaimer at any time without notice. When we make changes, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of the policy. 

**Contact Information**  
Please contact Onextrapixel by completing the form on the [Contact](http://www.onextrapixel.com/contact/) page or by emailing hello[@]onextrapixel[.]com if you have any concerns or questions.
